# ANUNKA MONDAL | CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGIST

718A Jogendra Gardens, Kolkata-700078 | +91 8707630503 | anunkamondal@gmail.com

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a RCI Licensed Clinical Psychologist and I have a year of experience in working with Children with Special Needs. I have had three years of experience working as a Clinical Psychologist. My experience and passion for this field keeps me going and looking forward to learn and expand my knowledge.

# **SKILLS**

- Psychological Assessments (IQ Assessment, Personality Assessment and Neuropsychological Assessment)
- Plan Psychological Intervention
- ∇Psychological Report Writing.
- Graphologist

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **YourDOST**

CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGIST (Consultant) | 08 February 2023- Currently Working

- Taking Online Sessions (Chat Session, Audio Session and Video Session)
- Taking Face to Face Sessions at IISc, Bangalore; TCS and Navi Technology, Bangalore.
- Conducting Psychological Assessments and making Reports for Each Session.
- Conducting Workshops and Seminars.

## Asha Hai

PSYCHOLOGIST | 01 September '2019 - 01 September '2020

- Take Special Education Sessions
- Make Home Based Plan for the children every month.
- Write Quarterly Report for the children.
- Plan and share Weekly Plan for the Special Education session with Supervisor.
- Handle Official Instagram and Facebook page of Asha Hai.

## **INTERNSHIPS**

- Richmond Fellowship Society, Lucknow (1 Week)
- National institute of mentally handicapped, Secundrabad, India (JUNE'2018)

# **CERTIFICATE COURSES**

- Kolkata institute of Graphology, Kolkata, India (Advanced course in Grapgology)
- Positive Psychiatry and Mental Health (COURSERA)

## **EDUCATION**

SECONDARY SCHOOL CBSE (2012-2014)

BA PSYCHOLOGY (HONOURS)
Calcutta University (2014-2017)

MA CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGY

Amity University (2017-2019)

M.PHIL IN CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGY

KGMU (2020-2022)